PREVIOUSLY, ON
"FRIDAY NIGHT TYKES"...
WHAT MAKES THE MISSION
MUSTANGS SPECIAL
IS JUST THE DISCIPLINE.
STOP ARGUING!
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
WE DON'T TREAT
THESE KIDS LIKE BABIES.
WE TREAT 'EM LIKE THEY'RE
A HIGH SCHOOL FOOTBALL TEAM.
WHAT IS THAT, MAN?
THAT WAS MY FAULT.
YEAH, GOOD.
NOW, FIX IT!
JEREMY, HE'S REALLY
GOTTA UNDERSTAND,
IF YOU'RE GONNA
BE THE LEADER,
THERE'S A LOT MORE
EXPECTED FROM YOU.
HEY, YOU'RE GOIN' TO
THE SEMI-FINALS
NEXT WEEK, GENTLEMEN.
[cheering]
MYZEL MILLER IN FOR HIS
SECOND TOUCHDOWN OF THE DAY.
THEY SHOULD BE PROUD TO CALL
THEMSELVES THE FIRST CHAMPS
OF THE SNOOP LEAGUE
OF TEXAS.
Y'ALL OUGHTA GET
SOME OF THAT!
[cheering]
HEY, WE'RE GOIN'
TO CALI, BABY.
- GO!
- PITCHES IT.
HE FUMBLES THE FOOTBALL!
IS EVERYTHING GONNA
GO BAD FOR US?
THE TEXAS WOLFPACK HAVE
DEFEATED THE YOAKUM OUTLAWZ.
I CAN'T BELIEVE WE GOT
FUCKIN' BEAT, MAN.
THIS IS
"FRIDAY NIGHT TYKES."
YOAKUM, TX
♪♪
THE SEASON ENDED A LOT EARLIER
THAN WHAT IT SHOULD HAVE.
MAN.
US COACHES TALK
EVERY DAY,
AND WE STILL CAN'T BELIEVE
THAT WE LOST THAT GAME.
LOAD ALL THIS STUFF UP.
BE READY
FOR NEXT YEAR.
ME, AND COACH DOUG,
AND ALL THE COACHES
WATCHED THE GAME OVER,
AND OVER, AND OVER.
AND IT'S LIKE,
YOU KNOW, WE WERE ON--
CHAD LEDLOW
YOAKUM HEAD COACH
INSIDE THE FIVE
YARD LINE TWICE.
CHAD LEDLOW
YOAKUM HEAD COACH
ALL WE HAD TO
DO WAS SCORE ONE TIME TO TIE IT.
YOU KNOW, GET
THE EXTRA POINT, WE WIN.
OUR BIGGEST POINT THIS YEAR,
COMIN' INTO TYFA
IS TRYIN' TO GET OUT THERE
THAT YOU DON'T HAVE
TO BE A HARD-ASS.
I MEAN, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO RUN 'EM 'TIL
THEY'RE PUKIN' EVERYWHERE.
BUT, AT THE SAME TIME,
MAYBE WE SHOULD'VE PRACTICED
A LITTLE BIT MORE.
THIS WAS ONE OF
THE LAST YEARS TOGETHER.
A LOT OF THE KIDS WILL
BE PLAYIN' JUNIOR HIGH
BALL NEXT YEAR,
AND SO IT'S
GONNA BE DIFFERENT.
♪♪
[dog barking]
MYZEL MILLER'S HOUSE
MYZEL?
YOU'RE NOT LITERALLY TAKING
ALL THEM SHOES, ARE YOU?
- WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
- WHY?
[chuckling]
BRIDGET LEE
MYZEL'S MOTHER
THEY ON THEY WAY
TO CALI, TO DO NATIONALS.
SEMI-FINALS, I BELIEVE,
FIRST, RIGHT?
- YEAH.
- SEMI-FINALS SATURDAY.
MYZEL MILLER
AND THEN SUNDAY IS
THE ACTUAL GAME.
YOU'RE WORSE THAN A GIRL.
YOU'RE NOT EVEN GONNA BE ABLE TO
WEAR ALL THESE SHOES.
- YES, I AM.
- I JUST DON'T SEE IT.
OKAY-- I DON'T WANNA
SMELL THEM SHOES.
JUJU THOMAS'S HOUSE
YOU GOT ALL YOUR
UNDERWEAR, UNDERSHIRTS?
YEP.
POLOS, T-SHIRTS,
JEANS, SOCKS?
- ALL RIGHT.
- YEAH-- WAIT. YEAH.
JUJU'S PRETTY EXCITED
ABOUT THE TRIP.
BRITTNEY HARRIS
JUJU'S MOTHER
UH, HE'S LOOKING FORWARD.
UH, IT'S A GOOD OPPORTUNITY.
JUJU THOMAS
JUST FLYIN' OUTTA
TOWN WITH THE TEAM
AND MAKIN' THAT BOND WITH
HIS TEAMMATES AND THE COACHES
IS JUST REALLY
GOOD FOR HIM.
TAKIN' A BLANKET,
TAKIN' A PILLOW.
YOU DONE HAD THAT EVER
SINCE YOU WAS ONE.
I'M EXCITED,
'CAUSE IT'S OUR FIRST TRIP
ACTUALLY ON A PLANE.
I'M A LITTLE NERVOUS, 'CAUSE
IT'S OUR FIRST TRIP ON A PLANE.
I'M SCARED.
WHAT YOU SCARED OF?
- YOU ALREADY KNOW.
- OF WHAT?
THE PLANE.
HE DON'T LIKE HEIGHTS,
BUT HE'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
ONCE YOU GET ON THERE
WITH THEM BOYS,
AND YA'LL GET TO TALKIN'
AND CUTTIN' UP,
YOU WON'T EVEN KNOW.
SO NOW, MOST IMPORTANTLY,
DO YOU HAVE YOUR CLEATS?
MM-HMM.
IT'S PRETTY AWESOME JUST TO,
LIKE, TO FLY OUTTA STATE
TO GO PLAY A FOOTBALL GAME,
'CAUSE, LIKE, NOT MANY KIDS
GET THAT OPPORTUNITY
TO GO DOWN AND PLAY--
AND GO PLAY
IN CALIFORNIA.
WE CAN MAKE
OUTLAW HISTORY.
HEY, WE GET
TO SEE SNOOP DOGG!
[laughing]
♪♪
MISSION VS HOUSTON
TYFA SEMI-FINAL
IF YOU WANT THE
GAME, IT'S IN YOUR HANDS.
GUYS, WANT IT.
ONE CHANCE,
THIS IS IT, GENTLEMEN,
TO DECIDE IF
YOU'RE PLAYIN' NEXT WEEK.
CHRIS VON WALD
MUSTANGS HEAD COACH
WHERE DO YOU
WANNA BE NEXT WEEKEND?
[all]
STATE CHAMPIONSHIP.
LET'S MAKE IT HAPPEN.
[all]
ONE, TWO,
THREE, MUSTANGS!
AND HERE IT IS,
THE DIVISION ONE
JUNIOR MATCH UP
BETWEEN THE NUMBER ONE SEED,
HOUSTON SEAHAWKS,
AND THE NUMBER FIVE SEED,
MISSION MUSTANGS.
JEREMY DURAN
MUSTANG QB
THIS IS YOUR SHOT.
TAKE OVER THIS GAME.
TAKE OVER.
JUST BE YOU.
THIS IS YOUR GAME.
THEY CAN'T STOP YOU.
QUARTERBACK NUMBER 11,
JEREMY DURAN,
LOOKING TO PASS.
IF YOU WANNA BE A LEADER,
IT'S THERE FOR YOU.
GO DO WHAT YOU GOTTA DO.
[cheers and applause]
I NEED BLOCKING,
RIGHT NOW, GENTLEMEN!
NO HOLDING!
NO MISTAKES!
DURAN HANDS IT OFF.
GOES OFF TACKLE,
FIGHTS HIS WAY,
AND HE'LL GET IT
IN THE END ZONE.
TOUCHDOWN!
[screaming]
LOUDER!
DURAN KEEPS IT HIMSELF.
SHOOTS UP THE MIDDLE.
GO, JEREMY! YES!
YOU CAN BE TIRED FOR
THE REST OF YOUR LIFE.
DON'T GET TIRED
ON ME, NOW!
HEY, YOU WANNA GO FOR
IT, RIGHT HERE, AND TRY
TO PUT HIM A WAY?
- YES, SIR.
- ALL RIGHT, LET'S DO IT.
DURAN GETS THE SNAP.
HE'LL HAND IT OFF,
AND HE'LL PUNCH IT
OFF TACKLE.
COME ON, DAMIEN.
[screaming]
ONE MAN TO BEAT,
AND HE DOES IT.
TOUCHDOWN, MUSTANGS!
[cheering]
AND IT'S OVER.
DONNA VON WALD
CHRIS' WIFE
AMAZING! AMAZING!
BACK IN THE 'SHIP, BABY!
- WE'RE GOIN' TO THE 'SHIP!
- BACK IN THE 'SHIP!
WE'RE GOIN' TO THE 'SHIP!
[all chanting]
[cheers and applause]
AND FOR THE SECOND YEAR
IN A ROW,
THE MISSION MUSTANGS ARE HEADED
TO THE STATE CHAMPIONSHIP,
AFTER UPSETTING
THE HOUSTON SEAHAWKS.
OUR GOLDEN TICKET
WAS PUNCHED, GENTLEMEN.
THIS IS OUR GOLDEN TICKET.
WE'RE GOIN' TO
THE STATE CHAMPIONSHIP.
THIS YEAR IS OURS.
NO MATTER WHAT, IT IS OURS,
RIGHT, GENTLEMEN?
[all]
YES, SIR!
WE'RE GONNA WIN STATE,
RIGHT, GENTLEMEN?
[all]
YES, SIR!
WE'RE GONNA WIN STATE,
RIGHT, GENTLEMEN?
[all]
YES, SIR!
AHH!
MUSTANG PRACTICE
PREP FOR WOLFPACK
[indistinct chatter]
HEY, LET'S GO!
GET YOUR HELMETS ON!
LET'S GO!
GENTLEMEN, DO YOU KNOW
WHAT THE WOLFPACK SAID
IN THE NEWSPAPER TODAY?
WHAT?
THEY SAID THEY'VE ALREADY
BEAT THE BEST TEAMS IN TEXAS.
HUT!
THEY'RE GONNA GET A CHANCE
TO PLAY THE BEST TEAM
THIS WEEKEND.
CHRIS VON WALD
MUSTANGS HEAD COACH
WE'RE PREPPING FOR
THE, UH, WOLFPACK.
IT'S THE STATE FINALS
OF TYFA.
JEREMY, THE FIRST HOLE
YOU SEE, YOU'RE GONE.
YOU KNOW THAT, RIGHT?
YES, SIR.
HUT!
JEREMY, I DON'T KNOW WHY
YOU'RE WAITING SO LONG
TO CALL, "HUT."
OMAR TRUJILLO
MUSTANGS O COORDINATOR
AS SOON AS DAMIEN
GETS PAST THE CENTER,
YELL "HUT,"
AND GO.
I'M NOT GONNA LIE.
WE'RE CONCERNED ABOUT
JEREMY BEING OVERCONFIDENT
BECAUSE IT'S CHAMPIONSHIP WEEK,
AND THIS IS SERIOUS.
I MEAN, WE'RE ON
A MISSION TO GET
WHAT WE SHOULD'VE
GOT LAST YEAR.
[indistinct yelling]
HUT!
TERRIBLE!
JEREMY'S FUCKIN'
CALLED "HUT," NOW,
BEFORE HE EVEN GOT
TO THE CENTER.
HOW HARD IS IT TO JUST
DO WHAT I ASK?
WHO RUNS THIS
MOTHERFUCKIN' OFFENSE?
- YOU.
- THANK YOU.
SO NOW, WE DO
WHAT I SAY.
HE'S THE LEADER
OF THE TEAM.
HE NEEDS TO UNDERSTAND
THAT WHAT HE IS SHOWING,
AND THE COCKINESS,
IF-IF HE BRINGS THAT ATTITUDE,
THE WOLFPACK ARE GOING
TO PUNCH YOU ALL DAY LONG,
AND YOU'RE NOT GONNA
BE READY FOR IT.
LET'S GO, JEREMY!
IF YOU DON'T HAVE IT NOW,
YOU'RE NOT GONNA
HAVE IT ANYWAY.
LET'S GO!
YOU'RE STEPPING HERE,
AND YOUR BODY'S
COMING THIS WAY,
AND YOU'RE TRYING
TO THROW OVER HERE.
YOU'RE NEVER GONNA
BE ACCURATE.
JEREMY, WHY ARE YOU
JUMPING AROUND?
- RUN!
- JEREMY, RUN!
TO WIN THE CHAMPIONSHIP,
YOU'VE GOTTA EARN IT.
THERE'S NO GUARANTEES
YOU'LL EVER BE IN
ANOTHER ONE
OF THESE AGAIN.
- HUT!
- YOU GUYS ARE SO SOFT.
[whistle blowing]
YOU NEED TO STOP
BEING SOFT.
YOU NEED TO BE AGGRESSIVE.
THERE'S A LOT OF
PRESSURE ON JEREMY
TO MAKE SURE THAT WE WILL
FINALLY BE CROWNED
STATE CHAMPIONS IN TYFA.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S WHAT
WE PLAN ON DOING.
WE WANNA BRING
THAT TROPHY HOME.
AND PLEASE DON'T MISS
THIS THROW, JEREMY,
'CAUSE IT IS
A CHEAP-ASS TOUCHDOWN
WE'RE GONNA PICK UP EASILY.
I GUARANTEE IT.
YOU CAN'T MISS THAT!
LET'S GO,
AGAIN, AGAIN, AGAIN!
♪♪
OUTLAWS HOTEL
FRED DAVIS
OUTLAWS HEAD COACH
YES, WE GOIN' ALL
THE WAY TO THE CHAMPIONSHIP.
YOU KNOW, MAKIN'
THE TRIP TO DALLAS,
WHICH IS ABOUT A FOUR
AND A HALF HOUR DRIVE,
GETTIN' ON A PLANE
AT 6:00 THIS MORNIN',
FLYIN' TO L.A.--
YA'LL CAN TAKE OUR STUFF
IN THE INSIDE.
THEN YA'LL CAN
COME BACK AND PLAY.
WE'RE TRYIN' TO GET
EVERYTHING TOGETHER
WITH THE HOTEL ROOMS,
RENTAL VEHICLES.
MYZEL FORGOT HIS HELMET
AND SHOULDER PADS?
AND I DON'T THINK ANYONE
HAS ACTUALLY
HAD THE OPPORTUNITY
TO SLEEP.
- I'M SLEEPY.
- I'M TIRED.
WE'VE BEEN UP SINCE
LAST NIGHT--
SINCE YESTERDAY,
BASICALLY.
YOU HAVE TO, LIKE--
HE DID IT.
WE WANT THE KIDS
TO ENJOY THEMSELVES.
YOU KNOW, WE DON'T WANNA MAKE
IT STRICTLY ABOUT FOOTBALL,
BECAUSE, A LOT OF THESE KIDS,
THIS IS THEIR FIRST OPPORTUNITY
TO ACTUALLY COME PLAY
FOOTBALL OUTSIDE OF TEXAS.
[happy shouting]
FOR A LOT OF THEM, IT WAS
THEIR FIRST TIME FLYIN'
ON A PLANE.
BELIEVE IT OR NOT, YOU KNOW,
A LOT OF THESE KIDS,
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
SOME OF THEM ARE STAYIN'
IN HOTEL ROOMS.
♪♪
[collective chatter]
WELL, I CAN TAKE THREE BOYS.
THAT'S WHY I'M ASKING.
I WAS GONNA TAKE THEM, TOO.
THIS WEEKEND, WE HAVE
TWO FOOTBALL GAMES
IN 24 HOURS.
WELL, WE HAVE TO WIN
A FOOTBALL GAME
IN ORDER TO PLAY IN
THE CHAMPIONSHIP.
SO, WE GOT TO GET
THIS WORKOUT IN TONIGHT.
YOU KNOW, MAKIN' THE TRIP
WAS DEFINITELY DRAININ',
SO THAT MAY BE SOMEWHAT
OF A-A DISADVANTAGE TO US.
BUT, YOU KNOW, LIKE I SAID,
AT THE END OF THE DAY,
IT-IT JUST CREATES A BETTER
STORY FOR US TO TELL.
[collective chatter]
♪♪
OUTLAWS PRACTICE
PREP FOR SYFL SEMI-FINAL GAME
THIS IS GONNA BE THE LAST
WALKTHROUGH WE HAVE
BEFORE GAME TIME.
I'M TELLIN' YOU,
THAT TRAVELIN'
WE BEEN DOIN',
CLAYTON GUILLORY
OUTLAWS ASST COACH
STAYIN' UP ALL NIGHT
ON THE PLANE,
IT WEARS ON THE BODY, IF YOU
DON'T GET THE KINKS OUT.
ALL THE PLAYIN'
STOPS RIGHT NOW
FOR THE NEXT HOUR
AND FIFTEEN MINUTES.
WHEN WE DONE WITH THIS,
THEN YA'LL CAN GO BACK
TO BEIN' KIDS,
BUT, RIGHT NOW,
WE ARE FOOTBALL PLAYERS.
EVERYBODY UNDERSTAND?
- YES, SIR.
THE VISION THAT SNOOP HAD
TO UNIFY THE ENTIRE COUNTRY
THROUGH YOUTH FOOTBALL
IS TREMENDOUS.
THIS THE FIRST SEASON
THAT THE SYFL
HAS HAD SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA,
NORTHERN CALIFORNIA, TEXAS,
AND COLORADO TOGETHER.
RIGHT NOW, WE'RE PLAYIN'
RICHMOND, CALIFORNIA.
MARECUS GOODLOE
OUTLAWS ASST COACH
WE HAVEN'T SEEN RICHMOND,
SO I DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT 'EM.
RICHMOND IS A POWER TEAM.
SO, JUST LIKE WHEN
WE FACED FAST CAMP.
IF COACH FRAYER CALL "BLOOD,"
WHAT ARE WE DOIN' ON THE END?
CRASHIN' HIS ASS IN.
ESTEBAN GILLORY
SA OUTLAWS CLAYTON'S SON
ESTEBAN, DO NOT GET CAUGHT
LOOKIN' IN THE BACKFIELD.
I DON'T GIVE A FUCK IF
THEY RUN, DIVE, POWER DIVE,
POWER DIVE FIFTY
FUCKIN' TIMES.
DON'T YOU RUN YOUR ASS
UP HERE FOR NO TACKLE.
ELIJAH, POWER SET
TO THIS SIDE.
WHO HAS THE TIGHT END?
LIKE, I'M AS EXCITED
AS SHIT, MAN.
I KNOW WE'RE MISSIN' CADEN.
WHO ELSE WE MISSIN'?
CADEN, MAN,
HE'S OUR QUARTERBACK.
FRED DAVIS
OUTLAWS HEAD COACH
AND, UH, HE'LL BE FLYIN'
IN TOMORROW MORNIN'.
DIEGO NAREZO
SA OUTLAWS BACKUP QB
LET'S GO, DIEGO.
WE'VE BEEN KNOWIN' FOR
SEVERAL WEEKS THAT CADEN
WOULDN'T BE HERE
FOR THESE FEW DAYS.
WE FEEL LIKE WE'RE A GREAT TEAM
WHEN CADE IS LEADIN' US.
SO, WITH THAT BEIN' SAID,
THAT'S NOT GONNA CHANGE
WHAT WE DO.
YOU KNOW, WE GONNA DO
WHAT HAS GOT US HERE.
YOU PICK ONE, DIEGO.
THEY BOTH RUNNIN' NINES.
DIEGO GONNA START
BECAUSE CADEN WAS OUTTA TOWN.
I MEAN, IT WASN'T
HIS FAULT OR NOTHIN'.
IT AIN'T NOTHIN' LIKE
HE DID ANYTHING WRONG.
HIS PARENTS TOOK HIM
OUTTA TOWN FOR A WEEK.
BUT, AT THE SAME TIME,
DIEGO'S AT PRACTICE ALL WEEK.
AND IF YOU--
IF IT WAS REVERSED,
IT'D HAVE BEEN
THE SAME SITUATION.
I MEAN, THAT'S NOT SAYIN'
CADEN'S NOT GONNA PLAY,
BECAUSE HE DEFINITELY
GONNA PLAY.
BUT DIEGO'S GONNA START.
JUJU?
GIVE ME FIRST DEFENSE.
FIRST DEFENSE, LET'S GO.
COME ON!
COME ON, GIMME LINEBACKER.
YEAH.
THEY GOT THEIR LITTLE SPIES
SITTIN' OVER THERE TOO.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH,
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
THAT MOTHERFUCKER,
HE LOOKIN' AT EVERYTHING.
THAT NIGGA LOOK DUMB
AS FUCK MAN.
THE REST OF THIS SHIT
WE CAN DO AT THE HOTEL, MAN.
JUST RUN SOME BULLSHIT.
LIKE, SOME BASIC SHIT.
IT AIN'T GOT NOTHIN'
TO DO WITH BEIN' SCARED.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYIN'?
EVERYTHING TO DO WITH
BEIN' STRATEGIC.
RIGHT HERE, ONE AT
A TIME, LINE IT UP.
WE JUST WANNA BE CAUTIOUS.
[whistle blowing]
SO, YOU KNOW, IT DOESN'T
MATTER IF THEY KNOW.
THEY STILL HAVE TO STOP IT,
BUT, YOU KNOW,
WE'RE NOT JUST GONNA
GIVE THEM THE PLAYBOOK
AND SAY, "HEY, COME STOP IT."
ALL RIGHT.
SO, LISTEN, MAN.
THIS IS JUST TO GET YOU GUYS
BACK INTO THE FLOW OF THINGS
AND TO MAKE YOU GUYS REMEMBER
WHAT WE'RE HERE FOR,
ALL RIGHT?
ONCE YA'LL GET BACK
TO YA'LL ROOMS, MAN,
KEEP YA'LL HANDS
TO YA'LL SELF.
AIN'T NO PUSHIN' AROUND,
NO HORSE PLAYIN', ALL RIGHT?
WE CAN'T AFFORD ANYONE
TO GET HURT UP THERE,
RUNNIN' AROUND PLAYIN'
AND ALL THIS OTHER STUFF.
YA'LL UNDERSTAND THAT?
- YES, SIR.
WE'RE GONNA EAT DINNER.
YOU GONNA WASH YOUR ASSES,
'CAUSE YOU STINK.
AND LIGHTS OUT AT 9:45.
TOMORROW'S GONNA
BE A BUSY DAY.
♪♪
WITH ONE MINUTE AND
FORTY SECONDS REMAINING,
THE OUTLAWS HAVE THEIR
FIRST LEAD OF THE DAY.
I WISH WE HAD
A TIME MACHINE.
UGH...
IT MAKES ME WANNA PUKE.
- WE HAD THIS GAME WON.
- MM-HMM.
DONNA VON WALD
CHRIS' WIFE
WE HAD IT WON.
WE WENT TO THE STATE
CHAMPIONSHIP LAST YEAR.
CHRIS VON WALD
MUSTANGS HEAD COACH
WE LOST THAT GAME IN
THE LAST MINUTE AGAINST
THE SAN ANTONIO OUTLAWS.
I THOUGHT WE WEREN'T
GONNA WATCH THIS.
[laughing]
I KNOW. I KNOW.
IT WAS BANNED
FROM OUR HOUSE.
- I KNOW.
- HOW DID IT COME BACK?
WE DAMN NEAR CAME BACK
AND WON THIS THING EVEN
AFTER THAT MOMENTUM SHIFT.
LOOK AT THAT BALL HE THREW.
NICE CATCH.
I CAN'T WATCH THIS.
[laughing]
YOU KNOW, LAST YEAR,
IT WAS SO DISAPPOINTING FOR US
BECAUSE THIS IS THE GROUP
THAT I STARTED COACHING WITH.
THESE 11-YEAR-OLDS
ARE MY FIRST GROUP.
AND, UH, IT WOULD JUST
BE ICING ON THE CAKE
FOR US TO WALK AWAY WITH
THE CHAMPIONSHIP TROPHY.
DURAN TAKES THE SNAP.
HE GOES NEAR SIDE.
IT'S INCOMPLETE!
THE OUTLAWS WILL WIN!
[groaning]
- THESE BOYS WANT IT BAD.
- THIS IS OUR YEAR.
THEY KNOW THEY'VE GOT
THE TEAM TO DO IT.
WE JUST GOTTA GET IT DONE.
♪♪
BERRY CENTER STADIUM
CYPRESS, TX
HEY, THIS STADIUM IS LEGIT.
TYFA STATE CHAMPIONSHIP
TX WOLFPACK VS MISSION MUSTANGS
Y'ALL READY, FELLAS?
[all]
YES, SIR!
Y'ALL READY?
[all]
YES, SIR!
NOW, GUYS,
I WANT YOU TO SEPARATE.
THINK ABOUT IT.
VISUALIZE WHAT
YOU NEED TO DO.
JEREMY DURAN
MUSTANG QB
JEREMY'S FEELING FINE,
THE SAME AS ALWAYS.
HE'S NOT REALLY HAVING
ANY ANXIETY OR NOTHIN'.
OMAR TRUJILLO
MUSTANG O COORDINATOR
I MEAN, HE JUST
COMES OUT READY TO PLAY.
WE TALK ABOUT THAT HE NEEDS
TO SLOW HIS MIND DOWN
TO LET HIS BODY MOVE FAST.
WHEN BOTH OF 'EM
ARE MOVIN' FAST,
YOU JUST CAN'T
GET MUCH DONE.
THIS GAME DOESN'T DEFINE
YOU AS A PLAYER.
EVERYBODY KNOWS
WHAT YOU CAN DO.
YOU PROVED
I DIDN'T DO IT FOR YOU.
YOU DID IT.
WE'RE JUST PLAYING FOOTBALL.
THAT'S IT.
[indistinct shouting]
[cheers and applause]
FROM THE RIO GRAND
VALLEY CHAPTER,
PLEASE WELCOME
THE TEXAS WOLFPACK!
♪♪
FROM THE RIO GRAND
VALLEY CHAPTER,
PLEASE WELCOME
THE DISTRICT CHAMPIONSHIPS,
MISSION MUSTANGS!
LET'S GO, BABY!
COME ON!
COME ON! GET DOWN!
SOMEBODY GRAB HIM.
LET'S GO!
COME ON, BABY!
COME ON!
TIME TO BRING IT!
TURN YOUR BACK TO 'EM!
TURN YOUR BACK
TO THEIR BULLSHIT.
WE DON'T CARE
ABOUT THE PIT BULLS.
WE'RE PIT BULL TRAINERS,
FELLAS.
WOLFPACK HAVE SOME BIG BOYS,
LIKE SOME MAN-SIZED BOYS.
THEY'RE GONNA BRING IT
TO OUR VALLEY KIDS.
THESE KIDS ARE HUNGRY,
AND THEY'RE READY TO GO.
THEY SAY THEY WANT SOME!
[all]
THEY DON'T WANT US!
BECAUSE IT IS AN
ALL VALLEY MATCH UP,
IT'S HISTORY EITHER WAY,
WHOEVER WINS THIS GAME,
BUT I DON'T WANT
ANOTHER VALLEY TEAM
TO TAKE WHAT WE'VE
BEEN WORKING FOR.
WOLFPACK!
EVERYBODY IS SAYING
THE TEAM TO WATCH OUT FOR
IN THE STATE,
THAT'S YOAKUM.
AND WE WERE ABLE
TO STUN 'EM.
DAVID GONZALES
WOLF PACK HEAD COACH
ONE MOTTO WE'VE HAD
IS ONE TEAM, ONE DREAM.
AND THESE GUYS,
THEY'VE EARNED THAT CHANCE
TO MAKE THAT DREAM
A REALITY.
LET'S GET THIS SHIT DONE,
ALL RIGHT, FELLAS?
IF YOU EXECUTE, I PROMISE YOU,
YOU'LL BE STATE CHAMPIONS
AT THE END
OF THIS EVENING.
UNDERSTAND?
[all]
YES, SIR!
THE MUSTANGS
BACK TO RECEIVE.
BUT THE STATE CHAMPIONSHIP
IS ABOUT TO GET UNDERWAY.
♪♪
LET'S GO. GO!
SET THE TONE!
LET'S GO, JEREMY!
- JEREMY DURAN
IN THE SHOTGUN.
- HUT!
HE'S GONNA KEEP IT.
NOWHERE TO GO.
HE'S BROUGHT DOWN
FOR A LOSS.
YES!
HUT!
DURAN FEELING PRESSURE.
AND THE BALL IS LOOSE!
IT'S RECOVERED BY
THE WOLFPACK.
♪♪
- BOOM! WHOO!
- JEREMY, ALREADY?
JEREMY, ONE MINUTE INTO
THE GAME AND ALREADY?
HEY, HEY, HEY,
SETTLE DOWN, DUDE!
- YOU'VE GOTTA SEE THAT.
- EVERYBODY LISTEN UP.
HERE WE GO.
WE'RE GONNA RUN
THAT TRICK PLAY.
NOW, LISTEN UP.
- COME ON, BOYS!
- GO, GO, GO, GO, GO!
WOLFPACK MAKING
A LATE SUBSTITUTION.
GET OFF THE FIELD!
GO! POLO!
- GO! THROW IT!
- OH, MY GOD!
- NATHAN MANGIA FAKED
COMING OUT OF THE GAME.
- YEAH!
SPLIT OUT AS
A WIDE RECEIVER
AND CATCHES
THE WIDE OPEN PASS.
I TOLD YOU! I TOLD YOU!
THEY'RE SNEAKING 'EM
OUT THERE.
HE CAN'T HEAR US.
[cheers and applause]
HOW STUPID CAN--
WHY ISN'T SOMEBODY TELLING
'EM ON THE DEFENSE?
HEY!
WORRY ABOUT THE OFFENSE.
NO, I'M TALKING
ABOUT JEREMY.
WHY ISN'T SOMEBODY ON
THE DEFENSE TELLING HIM?
HE DID.
HE DIDN'T GO.
- HE DID, HE DID.
- OH, MY GOD.
WOLFPACK THREATENING
DEEP IN MUSTANG TERRITORY.
AND IT'S A FUMBLE!
BALL, BALL,
BALL, BALL, BALL!
MUSTANGS FALL ON IT
AND GET A HUGE TURNOVER.
[cheers and applause]
OKAY, CAN YOU
SETTLE EVERYBODY DOWN
AND STAND OVER
THEIR BALL?
[chanting]
MUSTANGS!
HUT!
DURAN LOOKS TO THROW
AND HITS MARCO POLO CAVAZOS
- FOR A FIRST DOWN.
- HUT!
♪♪
GO, JEREMY! JEREMY!
DURAN LOOKS
TO BE IN TROUBLE.
GETS FREE.
HEADS TO THE SIDELINE.
HE'S IN A FOOT RACE.
DURAN TURNS THE CORNER
AND TAKES IT ALL THE WAY
FOR A TOUCHDOWN,
AND THE MUSTANGS
TAKE THE EARLY LEAD.
[cheers and applause]
WOLFPACK 0 - MUSTANGS 6
1ST QTR
IT'S A MUSTANGS TOUCHDOWN!
YEAH, LET'S DO IT!
LET'S GO, MUSTANGS!
SECOND QUARTER UNDERWAY.
MISSION WITH THE BALL.
THERE'S NO SAFETY.
- YOUR QUADS LEFT.
- QUADS LEFT.
HALF ROUND.
- HALF ROUND TO
A JAGUAR PASS?
- JAGUAR PASS.
WATCH. WE'RE GONNA
SCORE, RIGHT HERE.
- HUT!
- MUSTANGS IN THE SHOTGUN.
DURAN TAKES THE SNAP.
HE'S GONNA THROW,
AND HE HITS
A WIDE OPEN RECEIVER.
BOOM! CALLED IT.
TOLD YOU.
NUMBER 27, DAMIEN CORTEZ,
WITH A 55-YARD TOUCHDOWN.
WOLFPACK 0 - MUSTANGS 14
2ND QTR
JUST LISTEN TO ME, BRO,
AND I'LL TAKE YOU
TO THE PROMISE LAND.
PLEASE?
I THINK THEY WANT SOME.
[all]
THEY DON'T WANT NONE!
PUT THE GAME AWAY,
RIGHT NOW!
LATE IN THE FIRST HALF,
THE MUSTANGS ARE ONCE AGAIN
THREATENING IN
WOLFPACK TERRITORY.
HUT!
♪♪
- GO, JEREMY. GO, JEREMY!
GO, JEREMY!
- HE'S GONE.
JEREMY DURAN WITH HIS SECOND
TOUCHDOWN RUN OF THE GAME.
WOLFPACK 0 - MUSTANG 22
2ND QTR
KABOOM!
THAT'S HOW YOU TAKE
A GAME OVER, BABY.
AND AT HALFTIME, THE MUSTANGS
HOLD A COMMANDING LEAD.
YOU GUYS WANT
A [indistinct]?
[all]
THEY DON'T WANT US!
HEY! THAT IS WHAT
PLAYING HARD LOOKS LIKE.
LOOK!
YOU KEEP PLAYIN'
LIKE THAT, JEREMY.
THAT IS WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU GO ABOVE AND BEYOND,
AND YOU PLAY YOUR ASS OFF
FOR YOUR TEAM.
I WANT YOU ALL LOOKIN' LIKE
THAT THIS NEXT HALF.
UNDERSTAND?
[all]
YES, SIR.
COME HERE. COME HERE.
YOU'RE TWO QUARTERS
FROM YOUR GOAL, UNDERSTAND?
[all]
YES, SIR.
YOU'RE SICK,
OR YOU'RE JUST MAD?
I COULDN'T BREATH.
YOU'RE GOOD.
YOU GOTTA RELAX.
SLOW YOUR MIND.
TAKE DEEP BREATHS.
RELAX.
IT'S NOT A BIG DEAL.
♪♪
RELAX.
YOU'RE STILL--
I'M-I'M NOT GONNA KICK
YOU OUT THE HOUSE YET.
WE'LL DO THAT IN
A COUPLE OF YEARS.
- YES, SIR.
- LET'S GO.
♪♪
THE SECOND HALF OF
THIS TYFA STATE CHAMPIONSHIP
IS ABOUT TO GET UNDERWAY.
I'M SO PROUD
OF YOU, BRO.
YOU TOOK THIS TEAM,
YOU PUT 'EM ON YOUR BACK,
AND YOU'RE RUNNING
YOUR ASS OFF.
- YES, SIR.
- KEEP IT GOIN'.
- BE A FUCKIN' ANIMAL.
- HUT!
DURAN FAKES A HANDOFF,
AND HE'S GONNA
HEAD UP THE MIDDLE.
BOUNCES IT OUTSIDE.
BREAKS A TACKLE!
AND HE'S GONNA SCORE!
WOLFPACK 0 - MUSTANGS 29
3RD QTR
♪♪
OH, YEAH!
MAN,
I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
I-I WANNA JUST PUT
YOU IN MY LITTLE LAP,
RIGHT THERE, AND JUST--
I JUST WANNA PUNCH HIM,
THOUGH, MAN.
FOURTH QUARTER
UNDERWAY IN THIS TYFA
STATE CHAMPIONSHIP.
- MUSTANGS IN THE SHOTGUN.
- HUT!
TAKES THE SNAP.
AND DURAN IS GONNA KEEP IT.
GO, JEREMY!
JUST GO!
- GO, JEREMY! GO!
[indistinct shouting]
[laughing]
OH, MY GOD!
[cheers and applause]
[whistle blowing]
[horn blowing]
- HOO-HA!
- HA-HA!
DURAN DROPS BACK.
HE'S GONNA THROW FOR TWO.
♪♪
CAVAZOS HAULS IT IN,
AND THE MUSTANGS TAKE
A 30-POINT LEAD.
♪♪
[whistle blowing]
GO CELEBRATE, GUYS.
GO CELEBRATE!
WOLFPACK 7 - MUSTANGS 37
FINAL
YOU JUNIOR STATE CHAMPIONS,
[indistinct] TEAM,
YOUR MISSION MUSTANGS!
WE DID IT, BABY.
OH MY GOD, I'M SO FUCKIN'
HAPPY RIGHT NOW.
STATE CHAMPS, BABY!
STATE CHAMPS!
- YEAH!
- STATE CHAMPS!
- HOW DOES IT FEEL?
- [all] GOOD!
ALL RIGHT, BABY!
- WHO'S STATE CHAMPS?
- [all] WE ARE!
WHOO!
YOU MADE HISTORY TODAY.
THE FIRST RGV TEAM EVER
IN TYFA HISTORY
TO WIN A D-1
STATE CHAMPIONSHIP!
[cheering]
♪♪
CONGRADULATIONS, BROTHER.
THANK YOU.
THE FIRST TEAM FROM
THE RGV TO WIN IT ALL.
YES.
PERSONALLY, DOES
THE STATE CHAMPIONSHIP
MEAN A TON TO ME?
OH, IT'S NOT GONNA GO ON
MY RESUME ANYWHERE, RIGHT?
MY REWARD WAS
THE LOOKS ON THEIR FACES.
AND WE DON'T 'EM LIKE KIDS.
WE TREAT 'EM LIKE ADULTS.
FOR THESE KIDS,
WINNING IS THE REWARD
FOR COMING TO WORK
EVERY DAY,
AND I THINK THE EARLIER
YOU LEARN THAT IN LIFE,
THE-THE BETTER OFF YOU ARE.
NOW DO YOU KNOW WHY
I'M SO TOUGH ON YOU, JEREMY?
LISTEN, IF YOU THINK
THIS IS THE END POINT,
MAN, YOU'RE WRONG.
THIS IS THE START.
WE-- I'M BEING SERIOUS, BRO.
THIS IS NOT WHERE
YOU WANNA BE.
IF THIS IS THE ONLY PLACE
YOU WANNA BE,
THEN YOU'RE ON
THE WRONG PATH.
THIS IS THE START
OF WHERE YOU WANNA BE.
ALL THE STUFF BEFORE
WAS JUST GARBAGE.
THIS IS THE START.
NOW YOU'VE MADE
A NAME FOR YOURSELF.
THIS IS THE START.
NOW YOU'VE GOTTA
WORK HARDER AND DO MORE.
- YOU UNDERSTAND?
- YES, SIR.
GO OVER THERE.
SAY HI TO YOUR MOM.
GOOD JOB! GOOD JOB!
GOOD JOB!
♪♪
OUTLAWS HOTEL
[indistinct chatter]
HEY, OUTLAWS!
YO!
FRED DAVIS
OUTLAWS HEAD COACH
HEY, LET'S GO IN
AND PACK IT UP.
WE GOTTA GET
ON THE ROAD, MAN.
DON'T MOVE AROUND.
JUST STAND OUT
FRONT AND WAIT.
1 DAY TO SYFL SEMI-FINAL GAME
TODAY, WE HAVE A TOUR
SET UP TO THE ROSE BOWL.
- HEY, Y'ALL READY?
- YEAH.
TO BRING THESE GUYS TO ONE
OF THE MOST HISTORIC STADIUMS
IN COLLEGE FOOTBALL,
IT DEFINITELY MEANS A LOT.
ROSE BOWL
PASADENA, CA
LISTEN, PAY ATTENTION
TO WHAT I'M SAYIN'.
WE ARE GOIN' IN HERE
TO HAVE A TOUR.
CLAYTON GUILLORY
OUTLAWS ASST COACH
I WANT YOU GUYS TO HAVE FUN
AND ENJOY YOURSELVES,
BUT, AT THE END
OF THE DAY, REMEMBER,
SEDRICK "JUJU" THOMAS
OUTLAWS
YOU REPRESENT
THE SAN ANTONIO OUTLAWS.
THERE IT IS. LOOK.
CAN YOU SEE YOURSELF PLAYIN'
IN SOMETHIN' LIKE THIS, MAN?
♪♪
WE'RE HERE TODAY, LIKE,
KINDA GIVE THE KIDS A IDEA
OF COLLEGE ATMOSPHERE.
BEING ABLE TO SEE IT AND KNOW
THAT IT'S ACTUALLY THERE,
BRITNEY HARRIS
JUJU'S MOTHER
IT GIVES THEM, LIKE,
A WAY TO SET GOALS.
LIKE, MAN, I ACTUALLY WANNA
BE ABLE TO PLAY HERE
WHEN I GET OLDER.
AND THEN ME, AS A MOTHER,
OF COURSE, LIKE,
I WOULD LOVE FOR MY SON
TO BE GREAT LIKE THIS.
XION, THIS COULD BE YOU
ONE DAY, MAN.
THEY STILL GOT THE OPPORTUNITY
TO GO OUT AND WORK HARD
AND MAYBE PLAY
ON THIS FIELD ONE DAY,
AND THAT'S WHAT
WE'RE ALL HOPIN' FOR.
JUST IMAGINE,
IN A COUPLE YEARS,
MARECUS GOODLOE
OUTLAWS ASST COACH
WE CAN COME OUT HERE
AND WATCH ESTEBAN PLAY,
OR WATCH MYZEL PLAY,
OR WATCH ANY OF THESE KIDS
THAT'S PLAYIN' WITH US.
AND I'M HOPIN' THEY'RE
REALLY SOAKIN' IT ALL IN
OF WHAT ACTUALLY CAN
HAPPEN IN THE FUTURE.
LOOK, 2025, MAN, THIS COULD
BE ONE OF Y'ALL, MAN.
ALTHOUGH WE'RE HERE TO
PLAY FOOTBALL,
WIN, LOSE, OR DRAW, YOU KNOW,
THESE TYPE OF MEMORIES,
YOU JUST-- YOU
CAN'T BUY THESE.
[applause]
ONE, TWO, THREE.
[all]
OUTLAWS!
Y'ALL COME ON.
WE GOTTA GO OUT.
TIME TO GO.
♪♪
WELCOME TO THE SNOOP YOUTH
FOOTBALL LEAGUE SEMI-FINALS.
REPRESENTING
NORTHERN CALIFORNIA,
THE RICHMOND STEELERS
VERSUS THE SAN ANTONIO
OUTLAWS FROM TEXAS.
I FEEL CONFIDENT.
I FEEL VERY CONFIDENT.
CLAYTON GUILLORY
OUTLAWS ASST COACH
WE COME OUT HIGH INTENSITY,
LIKE WE DID IN
THE STATE CHAMPIONSHIP,
AND HANDLE OUR BUSINESS,
WE'LL BE PLAYIN' TOMORROW.
THE FIRST
NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIP
ERIC MARTIN
STEELERS HEAD COACH
OF THE SNOOP YOUTH
FOOTBALL LEAGUE.
EIGHT AND 0 THIS YEAR,
RICHMOND, CALIFORNIA FOOTBALL--
IF YOU HAVEN'T HEARD ABOUT IT,
YOU GONNA KNOW TODAY.
IT'S TIME TO GET
IN GAME MODE.
AIN'T NOTHIN'
CHANGED FOR US.
I DON'T GIVE A DAMN
IF WE'RE IN SAN ANTONIO,
IF WE IN ITALY,
IF WE IN AFRICA.
WE BALL OUT.
DOES EVERYBODY UNDERSTAND?
[all]
YES, SIR.
OH.
DIEGO NAREZO
SA OUTLAWS BACKUP QUARTERBACK
DIEGO, GO WITH
THE FIRST FOUR PLAYS.
JUST SCRIPT THE PLAYS
THAT WE RUNNIN'.
DIEGO GONNA START.
MARECUS GOODLOE
OUTLAWS ASST COACH
RIGHT NOW,
I'M CONFIDENT IN HIM.
MAN, HE HAD A GOOD WEEK
OF PRACTICE.
CADE'S READY, AS WELL.
CADEN BOSANKO
OUTLAWS STARTING QB #5
CADE'S GONNA PLAY.
CADEN HAS GOT US HERE,
SO WE DEFINITELY NOT GONNA
SHIT ON HIM, JUST BECAUSE
HE MISSED A WEEK OF PRACTICE
ON HIS FAMILY VACATION.
HEY, COME HERE, MAN.
FRED.
SINCE WE HAD THIS WAY
IN PRACTICE GOIN' LAST WEEK,
MAN, I'M GONNA START DIEGO
IN THE FIRST COUPLE SERIES.
OH, NO, MAN,
WE CAN'T DO THAT.
WE CAN'T DO THAT, MAN.
THIS THE BIGGEST GAME
OF THE SEASON, MAN.
MAN, WE CAN'T
START CADEN.
HE DIDN'T COME
TO PRACTICE ALL WEEK.
BUT WE KNEW THAT
GOIN' INTO IT.
BUT I GOTTA SCRIPT
THE PLAYS THAT I'M RUNNIN'--
THAT I'VE BEEN RUNNIN'
WITH HIM.
MAN, WE GOIN' BACK
TO THE SAME SHIT WE DID
I-I-IN THE BEGINNING
OF THE SEASON, MAN.
NOT WITH THAT FLIP-FLOP
SHIT, OR WHATEVER.
WE'RE NOT GOIN' BACK
TO NOTHIN', FRED.
- I'M-- NO.
- YES, WE ARE, MAN,
BECAUSE-BECAUSE THE TEAM
BELIEVES IN CADEN.
I'LL START CADEN.
I'LL START HIM.
I GOTTA GO SWITCH
EVERYTHING UP
I BEEN WORKIN' ON
ALL WEEK.
IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT, MAN.
- FUCK, MAN.
- WHAT'S WRONG NOW?
JUST PUT CADEN
IN THERE, MAN.
HUH?
JUST PUT CADEN IN THERE
AND TEACH HIM
THE FIRST FOUR PLAYS
THAT WE RUNNIN'.
GODDAMN, MAN.
I KNOW THIS SHIT DESTROY
THAT BOY, MAN.
FUCK!
ALL RIGHT, SO, WE HAVE
JUST BEEN INFORMED
OUR OFFENSIVE GAMEPLAN
NEEDS TO CHANGE.
IF YOU DON'T START THIS GAME,
DON'T GET UPSET.
KEEP YOUR HEAD UP.
YOU BEEN PLAYIN'
YOUR ASS OFF.
WE'RE GONNA GET YOU
IN THERE.
WHEN YOU GET IN THERE,
DO YOUR THING, ALL RIGHT?
- YES, SIR.
- ALL RIGHT?
ALL RIGHT.
RUN THE FIRST FOUR PLAYS.
I'M NOT GONNA TELL YOU
WHAT THEY ARE, MAN.
GO!
CADEN, YOU DON'T
THROW THAT BALL.
JUST RUN THAT, MAN.
I NEED YOU TO MAKE BETTER
DECISIONS IN THERE.
YES, SIR.
MARECUS, LOOK, MAN.
YOU CAN'T PUT HIM IN
A POSITION TO FAIL, MAN.
HE DON'T--
HE DON'T KNOW THE PLAYS.
I'M NOT TRYIN' TO PUT 'EM
IN A POSITION TO FAIL.
I'M PUTTIN'-- W-WHY WOULD
I WANNA COME HERE TO FAIL?
- WHAT SENSE DO THAT MAKE?
- MAN, OKAY, HE DON'T--
IT'S OBVIOUS HE DON'T
KNOW THE PLAYS, RIGHT?
IT'S OBVIOUS.
I JUST TOLD HIM
THE PLAYS OVER THERE.
THING IS, WE AL--
BUT WE ALWAYS--
I MEAN, REGARD--
AIN'T NO SENSE
IN DEBATIN' IT, MAN.
WHATEVER YOU SAY
IS WHAT WE GONNA DO.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW
WHAT I'M SAYIN'?
THERE AIN'T NO DEBATE.
I'M JUST SAYIN',
WE JUST DISAGREE.
AND WE GOTTA
AGREE TO DISAGREE.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO, MAN.
[air horn blowing]
LET'S GO.
COME ON, MAN,
WAKE YOUR ASSES UP!
♪♪
OUTLAWS...
THEY MAKE A JOKE
ABOUT "HOWDY."
LIKE WE RIDE HORSES
AND SHIT.
[laughter]
- HEY, YOU GUYS.
- THEY DON'T FUCKIN' RESPECT
YOU.
LET'S BREAK THESE PUNK-ASS
CALIFORNIA NIGGAS ASS.
CADEN, ROLL RIGHT,
26 NIKE, HIT TI--
IVAN ON THE TIGHT END CENTER.
[whistle blowing]
Y'ALL REMEMBER
THE SCRIPT TO PLAY?
- YES, SIR.
- FIRST AND TEN, OUTLAWS.
CADEN BOSANKO
UNDER CENTER.
HUT!
CADEN, WHAT THE HELL
YOU DOIN'?
- PASS BY BOSANKO.
- WHY DID YOU THROW THAT?
- INTERCEPTED.
- NO, NO! GODDAMN!
[whistle blowing]
STEELERS BALL HERE,
MIDFIELD.
♪♪
CADEN! SHIT.
DAMN.
THAT'S WHEN WE NEED DIEGO'S
HEIGHT CAUSE CADEN'S NOT TALL
ENOUGH TO SEE HIM.
I KNOW, I WISH I PUT HIM IN LAST
PLAY. CAUSE THAT SHIT WAS THERE!
STEELERS ON OUTLAWS' 34.
- PASS!
- PASS...
- COMPLETE.
- COME ON!
[whistle blowing]
STEELERS BALL
ON THE OUTLAWS' 15.
THEY NERVOUS.
[cheering]
EVERYBODY UP IN HERE!
WHO'S GONNA BE
THE GUY TO GO OUT THERE
AND MAKE THE BIG PLAY
TO WAKE EVERYBODY UP?
- SOMEBODY STEP UP!
- YES, SIR.
IF YOU A LEADER...
- LEAD!
- FIRST AND TEN, STEELERS.
HEY, I WANT THEM TO TALK
ABOUT XION LAGRANT
WHEN THIS GAME
OVER WITH.
- HUT!
- FUMBLE.
- FUMBLE! FUMBLE! FUMBLE!
- OH, THERE YOU GO!
RECOVERED BY THE OUTLAWS,
NUMBER 22, XION LAGRANT.
[whistle blowing]
THERE YOU GO, XION!
OFFENSE, LET'S GO!
HEY, LET'S GO.
HEY, MARECUS!
QUIT PLAYIN' AROUND WITH IT.
GET THIS SHIT GOIN'.
Y'ALL CALM-- Y'ALL CALM DOWN
OVER HERE, MAN.
GO PRO LEFT, 25 POWER.
WE FINE, MAN.
WE ARE FINE.
HUT!
HAND OFF TO NUMBER SIX,
MYZEL MILLER.
MOTHERFUCKER'S A MAN,
RIGHT THERE.
♪♪
OUTLAWS 7 - STEELERS 0
1ST QTR
TOUCHDOWN, OUTLAWS.
♪♪
HEY!
Y'ALL COME HERE, MAN.
IT'S NOT OVER.
THEY CAN'T BEAT US
WITH THAT ONE PERSON.
Y'ALL KNOW WHO
THE BALL GOIN' TO.
THEY GOT ONE PERSON.
Y'ALL TAKE THIS
ALL DAY.
FUCK UP NUMBER 6, ON THREE.
HEY, MAN!
MYZEL, KEEP WORKIN'!
THEY'RE NOT FITTIN'
TO GIVE UP!
KEEP WORKIN'!
OUTLAWS INTO
THE STEELER 31.
- HUT!
- HANDOFF TO MYZEL MILLER.
GET THERE, MYZEL!
GET YOUR JAM ON!
- GET TO THE HOLE!
- DAMN.
- FIRST AND GOAL, OUTLAWS.
- HUT!
GET IN THERE!
HANDOFF TO MYZEL MILLER.
TOUCHDOWN, OUTLAWS.
OUTLAWS 14 - STEELERS 0
2ND QTR
[applause]
DAMN.
ARE YOU GONNA KEEP
GIVIN' THAT UP?
[whistle blowing]
♪♪
DON'T GIVE THEM
OPPORTUNITY TO GET BACK
IN THIS GAME.
WHEN YOU JAB SOMEBODY
IN THE MOUTH,
YOU HIT THEIR ASS
WITH A KNOCKOUT BLOW.
FUMBLE-- RECOVERED
BY MYZEL MILLER.
YES, SIR. HE'S GONE.
OURLAWS 21 - STEELERS 0
2ND QTR
RETURNED FOR
AN OUTLAWS TOUCHDOWN.
- YES, SIR!
- HIKE!
LET'S CLOSE THEIR MOUTHS UP
FOR GOOD, RIGHT NOW.
NOBODY HERE RESPECTS YOU.
EARN YOUR RESPECT!
MYZEL MILLER WITH
HIS FOURTH TOUCHDOWN
OF THE GAME.
HELL YES!
FIVE SECONDS.
[whistle blows]
OUTLAWS!
- WE CAME.
- AND WE CONQUERED.
- WE SAW, AND WE CONQUERED.
- YEAH, WE CONQUERED.
OUTLAWS 40 - STEELERS 6
FINAL
FINAL SCORE,
OUTLAWS 40,
STEELERS 6.
[cheers and applause]
ALL RIGHT, MEN.
HEY, THAT WAS A GOOD GAME
OUT THERE TODAY, MAN.
21 HOURS TO SYFL
CHAMPIONSHIP GAME
THE TEAM WE PLAY TOMORROW,
WE'VE NEVER SEEN THEM.
TONIGHT IS GONNA BE VERY
IMPORTANT FOR YOU GUYS, RIGHT?
IF I CATCH YOU GUYS RUNNIN'
UP AND DOWN THE HALLWAYS,
THAT LETTIN' ME KNOW
THAT YOU GUYS AIN'T PUTTIN'
THE TEAM FIRST FOR
THIS CHAMPIONSHIP TOMORROW.
WE HAVE AN OPPORTUNITY
TO DO SOMETHIN'
THAT NO OTHER OUTLAW TEAM
HAS EVER DONE BEFORE.
MAKE HISTORY, AND IT'S
GONNA FEEL GOOD, MAN.
ALL RIGHT.
COACH, Y'ALL GOT ANYTHING?
FUCK CALIFORNIA.
FUCK CALIFORNIA,
THATS WHAT I FEEL.
[all]
ONE, TWO, THREE, OUTLAWS!
[cheers and applause]
♪♪
[indistinct chatter]
OUTLAWS
16 HOUR TO SYFL
CHAMPIONSHIP GAME
THE LONG BEACH PATRIOTS...
THEY'RE BIG UP FRONT.
NOW, THEY SWARM
TO THE BALL.
EVERYBODY'S SURROUNDED.
THEY LOOK VERY DISCIPLINED.
WE NEED TO BE FOCUSED.
DON'T BE UP ALL NIGHT.
GOT A LONG DAY TOMORROW.
WAKE UP, AND YOU NEED
TO EAT BREAKFAST.
MONEY DON'T GROW ON TREES,
SO YOU NEED TO EAT
THAT FREE GODDAMN BREAKFAST.
♪♪
2 HOURS BEFORE SYFL
NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIP GAME
[indistinct chatter]
♪♪
TIME TO GET PREPARED TO WIN A
NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIP.
PLAY OUTLAW FOOTBALL.
PLAY OUTLAW FOOTBALL AND LET'S
GO OUT THERE AND WIN.
THESE ARE OUR BROTHERS.
ESPECIALLY NEWCOMERS.
WE DEVELOPE THAT BROTHERHOOD, SO
WE GOTTA STICK WITH IT.
- LET'S SEE IT.
- HANDS UP.
OUTLAWS ON THREE.
[all]
ONE, TWO, THREE, OUTLAWS!
♪♪
STUBHUB CENTER
YEAH! YEAH!
♪♪
OUTLAWS VS PATRIOTS
SYFL CHAMPIONSHIP
HEY, EVERYBODY UP,
JUST REAL QUICK.
GOT SOMEBODY WANNA SAY
A FEW WORDS TO YOU GUYS, MAN.
♪♪
THIS IS THE BIG PAYOFF.
Y'ALL BEEN WORKIN'
ALL YEAR TO GET
SNOOP DOGG
SYFL FOUNDER
TO THIS NATIONAL
CHAMPIONSHIP GAME.
Y'ALL ARE HERE NOW.
GO OUT THERE AND HAVE
40 MINUTES OF GREAT FOOTBALL.
MAKE YOUR COACHES,
YOUR PARENTS,
MAKE EVERYBODY IN YOUR LIFE
PROUD OF YOU.
Y'ALL GO OUT THERE
AND HAVE A GREAT GAME.
I LOVE Y'ALL, AND I'LL
BE PRAYIN' FOR Y'ALL.
ALL RIGHT?
I LOVE SEEIN'
Y'ALL BALL, MAN.
Y'ALL HAVE SOME FUN
OUT THERE, MAN.
I'M GONNA BE ANNOUNCIN'
Y'ALL GAME,
SO DO SOMETHIN' SPECIAL,
SO I CAN SAY SOMETHIN'
ABOUT YOU.
ALL RIGHT?
[laughter]
♪♪
IT'S OUR TIME, BABY.
REMEMBER THAT.
YEAH, BABY.
WE WORKED HARD
THIS WHOLE SEASON
FOR THIS OPPORTUNITY.
MARECUS GOODLOE
OUTLAWS ASST COACH
READY FOR THE FIRST ANNUAL
SYFL NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIP.
CLAYTON GUILLORY
OUTLAWS ASST COACH
THIS IS YOUR CHANCE
AT GREATNESS, RIGHT NOW!
YOU GOTTA GO TAKE IT!
REPRESENTING CALIFORNIA,
HERE TO TAKE CARE OF BUSINESS.
IT'S UP TO YOU GUYS.
DON'T LET YOUR STATE
DOWN TODAY.
WE'RE PLAYIN'
A HELL OF A TEAM.
THIS IS THE REAL DEAL.
TONY BRAMLETT
PATRIOTS
I MEAN, NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIP
THE BIGGEST STAGE I BEEN ON.
HEY, LET'S MAKE HISTORY
TOGETHER, BABY.
LET'S MAKE HISTORY TOGETHER.
[yelling]
[indistinct shouting]
I LOVE IT.
WE'RE PLAYIN'
A GREAT TEAM.
I DIDN'T THINK THEY WAS
A GREAT TEAM 'TIL I SEEN
'EM YESTERDAY.
- THEY A GREAT TEAM.
- COME ON, ALAN, TURN UP!
THIS IS YOUR OPPORTUNITY!
PLAYIN' YESTERDAY,
IT ALLOWED THE PATRIOTS
TO SEE WHAT WE BRING
TO THE TABLE.
COME ON, DIEGO.
TURN UP!
I'M A LITTLE IRRITATED
WITH THE PROCESS.
I DON'T LIKE THE FACT THAT
MY KIDS HAVE LESS PREPARATION
TIME THAN THEY
HAVE HAD ALL YEAR.
THIS IS A OPPORTUNITY,
RIGHT HERE, MYZEL.
WE GAVE IBUPROFEN TO
EVERYONE THAT NEEDED IT.
BRANDY LAGRANT
XION'S MOM
- THEY ALL NEEDED IT.
- WE DID ICE BATHS.
FRED DAVIS
OUTLAWS HEAD COACH
FATIGUE DIDN'T LOOK IT
HAD GOTTEN THE BEST OF US,
BUT WE'LL SEE AFTER
THE FIRST HIT.
IF YOU GOT SOME BABIES
FROM TEXAS
ON THE FOOTBALL FIELD,
MAKE SOME NOISE.
[cheers and applause]
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO!
LET'S GO, BABY!
IF YOU GOT SOME BABIES
FROM LONG BEACH
ON THE FOOTBALL FIELD,
MAKE SOME NOISE.
[cheers and applause]
- BE SEEIN' YA, HOMIE.
- WE GONNA EAT, ALL RIGHT?
WE GONNA EAT.
LET'S GO.
IT'S YOU, BABY.
CADEN BOSANKO
OUTLAWS STARTING QB
HEY, CADEN! CADEN!
[indistinct chatter]
SUCK IT UP!
[whistle blows]
LET'S GO!
DIEGO NAREZO
SA OUTLAWS BACKUP QUARTERBACK
♪♪
HEY, LET'S GO.
RUN THE SCRIPT.
- HUT!
- I-FORMATION.
THEY'RE GOING
TO 27 TOSS TO MYZEL.
MYZEL HAS GOT BLOCKIN'.
♪♪
HE'S RUNNIN' RIGHT
THROUGH EVERYBODY.
- THIS KID IS INCREDIBLE!
- LEAVE HIM ALONE!
♪♪
MEAN, MEAN, MEAN,
MEAN, MEAN, MEAN, MEAN,
MEAN, MEAN!
TOUCHDOWN, TEXAS!
WHOO!
OUTLAWS 6 - PATRIOTS 0
1ST QTR
LET'S DO THIS!
LET'S DO IT AGAIN, BABY!
- GOTTA MAKE TACKLES.
- MYZEL, MYZEL.
- WE NEED THEM EXTRA POINTS.
HERE WE GO,
ONE EXTRA POINT.
MYZEL, GO SPECIAL
TO ESTEBAN!
BUT IF HE AIN'T OPEN,
RUN IT!
NOW, THEY'RE IN
THE BATMAN FORMATION.
- D-LINE, D-LINE, D-LINE!
- A LITTLE CONFUSION
ON DEFENSE.
MYZEL, GO, GO, GO, GO!
- HUT!
- GO, GO!
- RUN IT IN!
- RUN IT, RUN IT, RUN IT!
RUN IT, RUN IT!
- OH!
- YEAH!
WHAT'S THE FLAG FOR?
THEY'RE GONNA CALL THE FLAG
ON US, HIS JUMP, MAN.
NO, NO, NO, BULLSHIT.
WHAT WAS THE EXPLANATION?
THEY SAY YOU CAN'T HURDLE.
NIGGAS CALIFORNIA
CAN'T JUMP?
CALL IS HURDLING.
YOU CANNOT JUMP OVER
A PLAYER.
YOU CAN'T LEAVE YOUR FEET.
THEY DO IT IN THE NFL.
[laughing]
SNOOP IS ADVOCATING.
THAT'S A FOOTBALL MOVE.
YOU CAN'T DO THAT
IN THIS LEAGUE.
FUCKIN' BULLSHIT, MAN.
REGGIE BUSH BEEN DOIN'
THAT SHIT FOR YEARS.
THAT NIGGAS FROM CALIFORNIA.
I'M DOCKIN' Y'ALL PAY
FOR THAT, REF.
THAT AIN'T RIGHT.
THAT'S A BAD CALL.
THAT'S A FOOTBALL MOVE.
THANK YOU.
- THANK YOU, SNOOP!
- SHOTGUN FORMATION.
- OH, BAD SNAP.
- FUMBLE!
- LOST THE BALL.
- WE GOT THE BALL!
- OUTLAWS BALL.
WE GOT THE BALL!
YES, SIR!
- YES, SIR!
- YEAH, WE GOT THIS!
YES, SIR!
HEY, PUT SOME POINTS
ON THE BOARD, MAN.
- HUT!
- TACKLED BY 24.
[whistle blowing]
YOU DON'T NEED
TO BE THAT DEEP!
HUT!
DEEP BACK NUMBER 6,
MYZEL, AND HE'S TAKEN
AT THE LINE OF SCRIMMAGE,
BRINGING UP FOURTH DOWN.
IT'S FOURTH DOWN.
WE GOTTA FUCKIN'
THROW THE BALL, MAN.
DIEGO!
DIEGO, COME HERE!
YEAH, LET'S GO TO
THE QUARTERBACK.
NEVER KNOW WHEN YOUR NUMBER
IS GONNA BE CALLED.
Y'ALL LINE UP IN QUADS
OVER THERE.
FORWARD RECEIVER
IS OVER HERE.
ALAN, YOU'LL BE
BY YOURSELF.
EVERYBODY RUN NINES.
YOU RUN THE SIX.
HIT THE SIX.
YEAH, THEY'LL BE COMIN',
SO YOU GOTTA GET RID
OF IT QUICK.
LOOK, AND LOOK BACK AT ALAN
RUNNIN' THE SKINNY SAFETY.
YOU GUYS GOTTA
MAKE THE PLAY.
WHAT'S UP, DIEGO?
THEY PUT IN THE BACKUP
QUARTERBACK, NUMBER THREE.
THEY'RE GOIN' OFFENSE.
FOURTH DOWN
AND ABOUT FIFTEEN.
[whistle blowing]
OH, YEAH.
OH, YEAH, DIEGO.
DIEGO, YES.
♪♪
DIEGO! DIEGO!
OH, MY GOD,
NO, HE DIDN'T!
HELL YEAH.
THAT NIGGA
WENT OVER THERE.
NO, HE DIDN'T!
- ALL RIGHT, DIEGO!
- OH, YEAH! ALL RIGHT!
DIEGO, WAY TO GET OUT THERE
AND BALL OUT, OKAY?
HEY, MAN,
WAY TO WORK, MAN.
[whistle blowing]
OUTLAWS 13 - PATRIOTS 0
HALFTIME
GREAT CALL BY
THE OFFENSIVE COORDINATOR
- FROM THE OUTLAWS.
- LET'S GO.
WE GOIN' IN
THE LOCKER ROOM OR WHAT?
♪♪
LET'S GO.
WE GOTTA WORK, BABY!
WE GOTTA WORK!
OUTLAWS 13 - PATRIOTS 0
3RD QTR
SECOND HALF OF THE SNOOP YOUTH
FOOTBALL LEAGUE CHAMPIONSHIP
ABOUT TO GET UNDERWAY.
- LET'S GO, PATRIOTS!
- PATRIOTS AT THE 30.
- PASS!
- COME ON, ESTEBAN!
THE PASS
IS CAUGHT BY NUMBER 11
- AT THE ONE YARD LINE.
- HEY!
YOU GOTTA STAY AWAKE!
DO NOT LET UP!
ESTEBAN, IT'S GOOD, BRO.
FRED DAVIS
OUTLAWS HEAD COACH
OH, WE CANNOT LET THEM
COME BACK.
COME ON, MAN!
HANDOFF TO NUMBER ONE.
[whistle blowing]
OUTLAWS 13 - PATRIOTS 7
3RD QTR
[cheers and applause]
HE'S IN FOR THE TOUCHDOWN.
MAN, LOOK, HEY, WE--
HEY, WE GOTTA TAKE
THIS SHIT, MAN.
RIGHT NOW,
THE DEFENSE IS BENDIN',
BROKE, BROKE, BROKE.
HIKE!
CADEN BOSANKO HAND OFF
TO XION LAGRANT.
SHORT YARDAGE--
OUTLAWS FACE A FOURTH DOWN.
HIKE!
HAND OFF
TO MYZEL MILLER.
- TAKEN DOWN FOR A LOSS.
- OH!
WHAT THE HELL?
MARECUS GOODLOE
OUTLAWS ASST COACH
FINAL MINUTES OF THE 4TH QTR THE
OUTLAWS LEAD 13 - 7
IF WE WANT IT, WE GOTTA
FUCKIN' TAKE IT!
MAKE A GODDAMN PLAY!
HEY, HEY, HEY,
GET RID OF IT QUICK!
PASS!
STAY BACK!
QUARTERBACK HITS
NUMBER 11 ON THE STRING.
- GO BACK AND GET HIM!
- GODDAMN IT, MAN!
- TACKLE HIS ASS.
- HE'S UP THE SIDELINE.
GOTTA GET A FUCKIN'
STOP, MAN.
[whistle blowing]
TAKEN DOWN ACROSS MIDFIELD.
WE'RE NOT STAYIN'
AT HOME, MAN.
- WE'RE NOT BEIN' DISCIPLINED.
- HEY, LETS STEP UP GUYS.
MAN, WE GOTTA GET
A FUCKIN' STOP.
DAMN, WE NEED
TO GET THIS STOP.
HANDOFF TO NUMBER 25,
AND HE'S BROUGHT BACK.
- YEAH, ALAN!
- YES, SIR!
YES, SIR!
[whistle blowing]
TIME OUT, PATRIOTS,
THEIR FINAL TIME OUT.
YOU'RE GONNA WHEEL DOWN
THE SIDELINE.
SOON AS YOU FAKE IT,
DROP BACK. LET IT GO.
RUN IT, NOW.
WE'RE GONNA GET
A TOUCHDOWN.
HEY, LOOK, THIS IS
OUR TIME, RIGHT NOW.
THIS IS THE STANCE THAT'S
GONNA MAKE THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN US WINNING
AND LOSING THIS THE GAME.
THIS IS THE STANCE WE
GOTTA MAKE, RIGHT NOW!
CLAYTON GUILLORY
OUTLAWS ASST COACH
GO GET THIS.
GO GET THIS, MAN.
DEFENSE, STAY
IN THE GAME, BOYS!
WE NEED ONE PLAY!
DEFENSE, WE NEED ONE PLAY!
MYZEL, JUST STAY BACK!
YES!
BACK UP, BACK UP,
BACK UP, BACK UP.
MYZEL!
♪♪
PASS, PASS!
- YEAH!
- GET THERE, MYZEL!
AND BROKEN UP
BY MYZEL MILLER.
[whistle blowing]
OUTLAWS 13 - PATRIOTS 7
FINAL
[cheers and applause]
THE OUTLAWS WIN!
- HELL YEAH.
- HELL YES!
[collective chatter,
cheering]
HELL OF A TEAM, MAN.
HELL OF A COACHING, TOO, MAN.
YOU CAN'T TELL ME THAT
ANYBODY ON THIS PLANET
WOULDA DREW THAT SCRIPT UP
THE WAY THAT IT UNFOLDED.
THOSE KIDS DESERVE TO BE
NATIONAL CHAMPIONS.
[cheering]
♪♪
I FEEL LIKE WE WAS A GREAT
COACHING STAFF THIS YEAR.
BUT, MAN, WE DIDN'T
DO THAT TODAY.
- THE KIDS DID IT.
- OUTLAWS!
OUTLAWS!
[indistinct shouting]
HOW DID WE GIVE IT TO 'EM?
[all]
ALL DAY LONG!
♪♪
T.J.!
A LOT OF TIMES, PEOPLE,
THEY DON'T REALIZE
HOW MUCH ABILITY AND SKILLS
THEY HAVE UNTIL YOU PUSH THEM.
IT AIN'T GO THERE.
IT GOES OVER THERE GOES UP
ON THAT TOP SHELF.
I DON'T THINK I EVER TOOK
THE GAME TOO SERIOUSLY.
EVERYTHING YOU DO IN LIFE,
YOU SHOULD WANNA DO IT TO
THE BEST OF YOUR ABILITY.
SO, IF THAT'S TAKIN' IT
TOO SERIOUSLY, THEN, YES,
I'M TOO SERIOUS IN
EVERYTHING I DO.
[cheering]
OUR KIDS DREAM ABOUT
PLAYIN' VARSITY FOOTBALL.
[laughing]
IT'S GONNA BE AWESOME.
THEY'VE BEEN SO SUCCESSFUL
IN YOUTH FOOTBALL.
AND TO SEE THEM GROW UP
AND GO THROUGH JUNIOR HIGH
CHAD LEDLOW
YOAKUM HEAD COACH
AND HIGH SCHOOL, HOPEFULLY,
THAT SUCCESS CONTINUES.
YEAH, LET THE KIDS
BE KIDS, YOU KNOW?
HAVE FUN.
THAT'S WHAT IT'S ABOUT.
I THINK THAT'S WHY
OUR KIDS DO SO WELL.
AND NOW FOR THE PRESENTATION
OF THE SNOOP YOUTH FOOTBALL
LEAGUE NATIONAL
CHAMPIONSHIP TROPHY.
[applause]
CONGRATULATIONS ON BEHALF
OF THE SYFL.
WELCOME TO THE LEAGUE.
THANK YOU, THANK YOU,
THANK YOU.
HEY, Y'ALL TAKE THAT
AND PASS THAT AROUND, MAN.
[cheering]
ANOTHER ONE.
♪♪
HOW OUR SEASON WENT,
I DON'T THINK I WOULD
TRADE IT FOR ANYTHING.
YOU KNOW, I'VE HAD
SOME THINGS IN MY LIFE
THAT I'M NOT PROUD OF,
BUT IT'S ABOUT YOU
BEING ABLE TO COME BACK
BRUCE CHAMBLISS
SEAHAWKS HEAD COACH
FROM THOSE SORT OF THINGS.
YOU KNOW, YOU GOTTA HAVE
SOME RESILIENCY.
I TELL 'EM ALL THE TIME,
IF YOU GET KNOCKED DOWN,
YOU GOTTA GET BACK UP.
THAT'S JUST A FALL.
♪♪
I ALWAYS WANTED
FOOTBALL BOYS, SO...
LORI HURT
STORM HEAD COACH
[laughing]
I GOT THEM.
THESE KIDS ARE SPONGES.
THEY CAN LEARN EVERYTHING
AND ANYTHING AT THEIR AGES.
THE BEST WAY TO WORK
WITH KIDS IS NOT SCREAMING
AND YELLING AT THEM.
IT'S TRYING TO BE
ALONGSIDE OF THEM.
SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK,
JUSTICE,
IF THE TEXAS STORM TAKES
THE CHAMPIONSHIP NEXT YEAR?
UHHH...
[cheers and applause]
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
YOUR SNOOP YOUTH FOOTBALL
LEAGUE NATIONAL CHAMPIONS,
THE SAN ANTONIO OUTLAWS.
I'M NOT MOTIVATED
BY COMPETITION.
I'M MOTIVATED BY
THE UNLIMITED POTENTIAL
- OF MY OWN SUCCESS.
- HEY, HEY, HEY.
♪♪
THE BEST THING
ABOUT YOUTH SPORTS
IS WATCHING KIDS GROW.
BUT A LOT OF IT ISN'T ABOUT
THE YOUTH OR THE SPORTS.
IT'S ABOUT THE GROWNUPS
AND THEIR DESIRES
AND THEIR WANTS.
♪♪
I THINK THAT SOMETIMES
YOUTH SPORTS IS UGLY.
♪♪
IT SEEMS LIKE,
EVERY SEASON,
WE COME BACK
TO THE SAME QUESTION,
AND THAT'S ARE WE DOIN'
WHAT'S RIGHT FOR OUR KID?
YOU CAN'T HELP BUT WONDER--
DID WE DO IT RIGHT?
♪♪
I DON'T KNOW.